can't i can't let this rest that y'all kept saying oh they look like the same man these are not
people that look alike these niggas do not look alike they acted alike but they do not look alike
and i just i made a whole vulnerable video and there were so many comments of you have a type
my type is narcissist and baby those come in all different shades shapes and sizes so here's a
really complex thing that i that i have to do people may disagree but people can love you and
harm you parents do it all the time i know both of those men love me i saw the way they looked at me
i know because i'm also an empath it doesn't change the fact though that they were unable to love me
wholly they did not love themselves but their impediments and trauma were so much greater
than their ability to be able to love me love itself is complex it's a feeling it's an emotion
it's a psychology like it is not simply just one piece of those things people can love you
however the layers of trauma in front of them are what they're navigating through every single day
that trauma creates shame that trauma creates a lack of self-worth that trauma creates a fight or
flight mechanism it creates a bunch of things that make actual love on all different levels impossible
and so something that happens is amongst all of those things folks start to treat you shitty because
they are so frustrated with their inability to get through those walls to give you the love and to
feel the love and if you're someone like me you have empathy for that and you will try to stick it out
because you want them to get to experience that however
you can't make somebody do what they got to do for themselves change of behavior does not change the
core cause and so it will always revert back this is why no matter how much trauma we have experienced
if we are not moving through those layers and creating a pathway to our soul's purity and joy
we're not going to be able to receive the love that we deserve and we're not going to be able to give it
either you understand me so they may have a very difficult path to get through to be able to love you
and you may have the same it is your individual responsibilities to do the work that you need
to do to get through and in the best case scenario each of you know that work is necessary and you
support each other through it however that's often not the case people heal at different rates but there
has to be an actual effort to heal or else what are we talking about that's why i'm on a 10-year hiatus
so i can cleanse that out of me and heal it out of me and if you're curious with therapy
with energy work with a connection to nature with a connection to my altar and my ancestors
with self-exploration of my own traumas and acknowledgement of codependency issues
and where they stem from so i don't want to be vague this thing takes work but it's so worth it
they don't look alike
you